uzood.com 2014-12-12

# uZood - Free Video Sharing Community.

Privacy Policy

Privacy Statement for uZood.com

UZOOD.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: UZOOD.com

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit <http://valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml>

Personal Information

Any information we collect, including your e-mail and mailing address, are not shared with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes except where explicitly implied.

External Links

This site contains links to other sites. UZOOD.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Public Forums and FAQ

This site makes forums, message boards, and FAQ groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Security

UZOOD.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. No one can view your account information without your password, which you can change anytime you want.

Contacting the website

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can Contact us at: info[at]uzood[dot]com

Copyright © 2014 uZood. All rights reserved.

Videos presented in this site are embedded from major video sharing sites like YouTube.com, Dailymotion.com etc.  
uZood.com doesn't host any videos and can not be held responsible for the content.
